

# KEY SKILLS

# PROGRAMMING

- « C
- « C++
- ~ WPF
- ~ PHP
- « Xaml
- « Telerík
- « Java
- ≈ PU/Sal
- « Línux

# WEB DEVELOPMENT

- « CSS
- ≈ HTML
- « Magento
- « MS Office
- « Word press
- « Corel Draw
- « MS Presentation
- Adobe Photoshop

# LEADERSHIP

- « Lead Meetings
- « Counseling
- « Motivation
- Event Organization

#### INTERESTS

- « Music
- « Travelling
- « Swimming
- Sketching
- Collection
- « Meditation
- « Classical Flute
- Reading Stuff
- ~ Trending Technology

# SHUBHAM DWIVEDI

dwivedishubham05@gmail.com +91-7837782507 Flat no 1104, Sneha Sadan CHS, Laxmi Nagar, Ghatkopar (west) MUMBAI- 400084



#### PERSONAL STATEMENT -

I'm an accomplished person with a background in Web Development as well as Desktop Application Development Technologies of more than one and half years.

Being a quick learner i have an in-depth knowledge of development and maintenance. I am looking forward to expand my experience within a role that combines new builds as well as products that can enhance and upgrade my skills to desired role.

#### **EMPLOYMENT**

#### "Total experience Three and half years"

- ♣ Worked as a System engineer at TCS in Banking and finance Services Bfs Domain for CCIL On payroll of IDC Technologies pvt ltd. (June 2018)
- Worked as a Software/Web UI Developer at Solo Luxury Mumbai (Sept 2017 – April 2018)
- Worked as a Software Developer at T.Tantra Joy Process Ltd. Mumbai (Jan 2017-Sept 2017)
- Worked as a website developer for 1.9 years at NanoTech Infosystems in Amritsar (Jan 2014-Nov 2015)

#### **EDUCATION**

- **♣ MCA** from Guru Nanak Dev University with 7.11 CGPA (2014-2017)
- Khalsa College affiliated to Guru Nanak Dev University (GNDU). BCA with 61% (2011-2014).
- DAV School (PSEB board)
  INTERMEDIATE in non-medical with 60%.(2011)
- St. Francis School (ICSE board) Matric with 69%.(2009)

## ADDITIONAL QUALIFICATION & CERTIFICATIONS

- Certified in JAVA SE6 from Oracle.
- **♣** Sangeet **Vibhushan** from **Praacheen Kala Kendran** in instrumental classical music on **flute**.
- Classical Music Under guidance of Pt. Hariprasad Chaurasia ji.

# <u>Languages Kown</u>

- English
- > Hindi
- > Punjabi

#### **PROJECTS**

#### • www.sololuxury.co.in [LIVE]

This was an e commerce portal in Magento for this company which deals with luxury brands like Gucci, Prada etc. The import goods from these brands and sell them directly to the consumer through there e commerce portal .Technology used were HTML CSS JAVASCRIPT BOOTSTRAP and many plugins available for Magento.

#### www.sproutedsystems.in\_[LIVE]

Technology used were **HTML CSS JAVASCRIPT BOOTSTRAP In PHP**.

### www.sroutedsystems.in/gadgelamp

Technology used were **HTML CSS JAVASCRIPT BOOTSTRAP In PHP**.

#### → www.ttantra.com [LIVE]

Technology used were **HTML CSS JAVASCRIPT BOOTSTRAP in PHP.** 

#### Brintons Carpet Asia Pvt. Ltd.

Brinton is a carpet manufacturing company whose Indian head office is located in Pune. I build an offline portal of its whole range of carpets. The technology I used was HTML, CSS, BOOTSTRAP, JAVA and MS ACCESS as the database at the backend. It was a full fledge portal in which user needed to login and nd go through the range of series and then make a purchase. User authentication was also used so as to prevent any unauthorized user from access.

#### • www.harindersohal.com

This website was based on a music director here in Amritsar. Its main objective was to highlight the complete profile of him. Its basic objective was the exposure of the work developed by him. So along with his achievements and history a multimedia portal was also to be developed so the user may browse and download from the list of audio and video. Technology used were **HTML CSS JAVASCRIPT BOOTSTRAP in WORDPRESS** 

## • www.beaconfinacial.ca [LIVE]

This website was based on a Canadian based financial company. While doing this project got an opportunity to work with the parallax Technology along with HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, BOOTSTRAP IN WORDPRESS

#### www.anythingfence.com [LIVE]

This project was based on word press technology which was customized according to the users demand. Technology used were **HTML CSS JAVASCRIPT BOOTSTRAP in WORDPRESS** 

#### Marad Sangeet Sarita [BOOK COVER]

Designed a cover for book based on raga and classical music. The main focus of the cover was to emphasize the tittle of the book. I used **Photoshop**, **CorelDraw**, **adobe Flexpro**.

# PERSONAL DETAILS

I'm a resident of Amritsar (Punjab) grown with love and care of my Parents Mr. Vijay Kumar Dwivedi and Mrs. Ragini Dwivedi. I was born on 5th APRIL, 1993 in my hometown Amritsar (Punjab). As being their loving and responsible son it's my aim to up bring the name of my parents and make them and myself proud.